const quizData = { 
    questions: [
        {
            question: "If a product costs $100 after a 20% discount, what was its original price?",
            answers: [
                "$234",
                "$125",
                "$543",
                "$132"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "How many unique 4-digit PIN codes are possible if each digit can be any number from 0 to 9?",
            answers: [
                "11,000",
                "4000",
                "9000",
                "10000"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "If a program executes 25 operations per second, how many operations will it complete in 5 minutes?",
            answers: [
                "6,500",
                "5,500",
                "7,500",
                "8,500"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "A mobile app download speed is 8 Mbps. How long does it take to download a 400 MB file in minutes?",
            answers: [
                "2 minutes",
                "3 minutes",
                "4 minutes",
                "5 minutes "
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "If a dataset contains 250 entries, and 20% of them are outliers, how many entries are outliers?",
            answers: [
                "30",
                "40",
                "50",
                "60",
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "If a shirt originally costs $45 and is on sale for 30% off, what is the sale price? ",
            answers: [
                "$31.50",
                "$35.10",
                "$36.10",
                "$31.60"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "A classroom has 35 students, and the teacher wants to distribute 525 pencils equally among them. How many pencils will each student receive?",
            answers: [
                "10 pencils",
                "13 pencils",
                "17 pencils",
                "15 pencils "
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "A software program uses 256 MB of RAM. How many programs can run simultaneously in 2 GB (1 GB = 1024 MB) of RAM without overloading the memory?",
            answers: [
                "4 programs",
                "6 programs",
                "8 programs",
                "10 programs ."
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "If a train travels at a speed of 80 miles per hour, how long will it take to cover a distance of 320 miles?",
            answers: [
                "2 hours",
                "4 hours",
                "6 hours",
                "10 hours "
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "You have a rectangular garden that is 12 feet long and 8 feet wide. What is the perimeter of the garden?",
            answers: [
                "40 feet",
                "50 feet",
                "60 feet",
                "70 feet "
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Jack and Jill have 44 cookies together. Jack has three times more cookies than Jill. How many cookies does he have?",
            answers: [
                "9",
                "11",
                "22",
                "33"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "53 is 25% of what number?",
            answers: [
                "13.25",
                "92.75",
                "141.5",
                "212"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "If you buy a notebook for $8 and sell it for $10, what is your profit percentage?",
            answers: [
                "20%",
                "25%",
                "30%",
                "15%"
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "A car rental company offers two payment plans for renting a car for a day: Plan A: $50 per day with unlimited mileage. Plan B: $20 per day plus $0.15 per mile driven.If you plan to drive 200 miles in one day, which plan is cheaper?",
            answers: [
                "Plan A",
                "Plan B",
                "Both plans cost the same.",
                "Insufficient information to determine.",
            ],
            correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        }
    ]
}

export default quizData;